♪ In the not-too-distant future ♪
♪ Way down in Deep 13 ♪
♪ Dr. Forrester and TV's Frank ♪
♪ Were hatching an evil scheme ♪
♪ They hired a temp
by the name of Mike ♪
♪ Just a regular joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ Their experiment needed
a good test case ♪
♪ So they conked him
on the noggin ♪
♪ And they shot him into space ♪
Get me down!
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
- ♪ The worst we can find ♪
- ♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
- ♪ And we'll monitor his mind ♪
- ♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ Now, keep in mind
Mike can't control ♪
- ♪ Where the movies begin or end ♪
- ♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ He'll try to keep his sanity ♪
♪ With the help
of his robot friends ♪
Robot roll call.
- Cambot.
- Show yourself.
- Gypsy.
- I'm not ready.
- Tom Servo.
- Hello, there.
- Cro-o-o-o-w!
- That's one "o"!
♪ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes ♪
- ♪ And other science facts ♪
- ♪ La, la, la ♪
♪ Just repeat to yourself,
"It's just a show ♪
♪ "I should really just relax ♪
♪ For 'Mystery Science
Theater 3000'!" ♪
- ( whistling )
- Ow! Ow!
Hi, everyone.
Mike Nelson here,
just giving Crow T. Robot
his regularly scheduled
maintenance check-up.
- Help me.
- You know what?
I think I got to sand your contacts.
Does that sound right?
Maybe change
your plugs and points.
- I have no idea what I'm doing.
- Please stop.
Say, Mike, maybe you should
take Crow to a certified mechanic.
I mean this is
highly specialized work.
Well, I'd like to,
but we're stranded in space.
Oh, yeah. Well, then try cutting
that big blue wire.
- Oh, God.
- No, no, I think I got it.
All I got to do is clip this little
thingamabob over here.
- Maybe it's this other thing here.
- Yeah, try that.
Oh, jeez.
Mike, you shouldn't have done that.
I feel funny.
Oh-- Oh, jeez! Oh!
( wheezing laugh )
Mr. Kotter! Mr. Kotter!
My God, man! You've turned him
into Arnold Horshack!
- Oh, my God.
- Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh, Mr. Kotter!
I can walk! Oh!
( wheezing laugh )
♪♪
Oh! Oh! Oh!
( wheezing laugh )
( gags, coughs )
Oh, thanks, Gyps.
That's got it.
You got me back to normal.
I don't think I could've stood
being Horshack
for another minute.
Yeah, let's face it,
a little Horshack goes a long way.
- True, true.
- Mommy! Mommy!
Wow, guys, it was terrible.
Mike was trying to repair me.
I came this close
to becoming Epstein.
I think the stress
of being trapped in space
might be getting to Mike.
♪ Love is like a butterfly ♪
Hey, what's going on, you guys?
Oh, hi, Mike. How are you...
Hey, you're ripping up
my Underoos!
Yeah, it's all part
of my ingenious escape plan.
Tearing up all the sheets
on the Satellite of Love.
Gonna throw 'em out
and climb back down to Earth.
Oh, that's great, Mike,
but why must my Underoos
be sacrificed?
Well, I ran out of sheets.
I had to use whatever
I could find. Sorry.
- Poor guy.
- Hey, my sensible pants.
Hey, my bra!
What do you know.
Hey, my panty ho--
I mean, what are those?
( chuckling )
You know, you guys, in my head,
I know I'm being impractical,
but in my heart,
I had to give it a shot.
That's really sweet, Mike.
You're an inspiration.
- Oh, I'll say.
- There's just one little thing.
What about my Underoos?
You owe me one pair of Underoos!
I want my Underoos!
Panties! Panties!
( laughing )
I got 'em!
Hello, my Underoo-wearing,
Horshack-imitating
young friends.
Say, you remember
"rock climbing," hmm?
And what about "deep hurting?"
Hmm? Hmm?
Well, I've come up with a process
that takes those concepts
one step further.
And to help explain it,
I've enlisted the help
of an expert,
one Dr. Felix Frankenhooker.
( German Accent )
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
That's enough.
Well, the process that
the good doctor here referred to
is a little thing that we like to call
"hypno helio static stasis."
So tell me, doctor, how does
hypno helio static stasis work?
Well, hypno helio static stasis
contains... X-4,
an extremely rare,
extremely scientific form
of subliminal poopy.
It can take a film like,
oh, how you say,
"Fire Maidens of Outer Space,"
slow it down,
remove all of the action.
Well, how does
hypno helio static stasis differ
from, say, deep hurt?
- Aha!
See for yourself.
Uh... Uh...
( normal voice )
Maybe you should tell
Mike and the bots about...
( German accent )
I mean, maybe you should tell
Mike and the bots about,
how you say,
this week's experiment.
I'll be glad to.
Your movie this week
is called "Radar Secret Service."
"In the Line of Fire," it ain't.
But first, a little train wreck
of a short called
"Last Clear Chance,"
and they're both packed chock-full
of hypno helio static stasis.
- Containing X-4!
- ( mutters )
- ( chuckling )
- More?
Ah, that's it.
Keep 'em coming.
- This is wrong.
- ( buzzer sounds )
Oh, we got movie sign!
( giggling )
Weird, is all. Weird.
Your last clear chance
for fantastic savings!
( chuckles )
That's what it is.
- What?
- I can't look at you.
♪ The National Safety Council ♪
Hmm?
( chuckles )
Ah, Jack Kevorkian throws
a tailgating party.
Save some for me.
Oh, look.
The Pepto-Bismol car.
"Never let this happen to you.
"Don't make the mistake
these people made.
Don't die."
( imitates radio squawk )
"Uh, when lilacs last
in the dooryard bloom'd..."
Narrator: I suppose I should've
gone in for a few minutes,
but I just couldn't do it.
Because of the tear
in the sprocket holes.
Burying someone from a family,
someone cut down
in the prime of life,
- Is one of the perks of this job.
- well, it's hard to take.
I could say good-bye
from here.
Good-bye! Oh.
Besides, I could do
more good out on the road,
and I could keep trying
to prevent other people
from killing themselves
in their cars,
- ♪ Don't cry out loud ♪
- and bringing to other families
- like the Dixons in there,
- ♪ Just keep it inside ♪
that heartbreak
that never quite heals.
Like psoriasis.
It was hard to believe that
just a few days before,
I was being spanked
by Rod McKuen.
the Dixon family had been
as happy and contented
a group of people
as you'd find anywhere.
Then I showed up.
Frank, Jr. had just
come home from college
( imitates motor racing )
to give his dad a little help
on the farm for the summer.
Ever since the heart attack,
Dad thought he was a basket weaver.
He was a chip
off the old block,
studying scientific
agriculture at school
and getting ready to follow
in his dad's footsteps.
♪ Longer than
there've been stars... ♪
Frank's girl, Betty Hutchins,
had been waiting for him,
of course.
Of course.
Everyone knew they'd be
getting married before too long.
- "When will we be getting married?"
- "Before too long."
Mr. Dixon's new tractor
had just arrived
down at the Union Pacific
freight station,
and they all went down
to inspect it.
You can guess there's
not much going on in this town.
...had just taken
his driving test the week before.
Alan sure wanted to
drive his dad's new tractor,
but until he actually
received a license,
Dad Dixon wasn't
letting him on the highway,
not even on a tractor.
You're not ready
for the high life yet.
These are fruits
you must not taste.
Me?
Oh! Oh, do we dare?
I feel so free!
He's off the ramp.
The U.P. station agent
had reminded Frank
that the 411 streamliner
was due any minute.
And of course, with Betty there,
he wasn't taking chances anyway.
Of course, when he's with Cindy,
he don't care!
...that careful all the time,
well, a lot of people
in the cemeteries
- would be alive today.
- That's all I'm saying.
Hey, my "Advocate" is here!
It was the next Monday
that Alan Dixon's
first driver's license arrived
in the noon mail delivery.
Boy, was he proud
of that license!
He couldn't wait to
show it to his brother.
"My arm's caught!
Be right there!"
...first license is
sort of a milestone.
It means all the roads
are now open to you.
♪ Bless this beautiful day ♪
( vocalizing )
...and, just as naturally,
wanted to make use of it
on any errand
that his dad or his mother
or his grandfather...
"I danced to Flo Ziegfeld,
you know?"
The only trouble was,
I had to choose that moment
to drive in and spoil things.
"Oh, it's the heat.
Hide the stash."
Of course, when you've
know a family
as long as I'd known the Dixons,
they don't treat you
as a cop but as a friend.
- "I thought we were all paid up."
- "Gonna need another 50.
Real shame if something
happened to this land."
Looks like you're gonna have
another Dixon to worry about.
- Alan got his driver's license.
- Oh, is that right?
( goofy chuckle )
"Yeah, my license."
You bet.
"Let me see that.
You're not a black female."
Well, I guess that makes it official.
When did you get it?
- Just came today.
- ( goofy chuckle )
Oh, just today, huh?
Why did I see you out driving
on Highway 30 yesterday morning?
( gasps )
"I have no son."
It was my fault.
I let him take the car
to go and see his girl.
- I'm sorry.
- Mother: You shouldn't have.
Fine way to be starting
your driving career.
Violation already.
"You're spending the night in the barn
with your crazy cousin."
I'm sorry.
Well, it's only a technical violation.
I didn't come here
to arrest you, Alan.
I knew you'd be getting
that license any day now,
and I thought this would
be a good time to come by
and tell you a few of
the facts of life
about driving before
you get started.
"You see, when a man
loves a car very much,
you recline the seat back,
you take the car--"
Now, these are accident reports
from my headquarters.
"Officer, is this gonna take long?
Each figure represents
someone injured or killed...
"We got a crop out in the field
we got to cut--
- on city streets, farm roads,
- "It's getting late.
highways and railway crossings.
"We've got to mow that hay.
Got to get it to market.
All the facts
and figures are here.
We lose money if we don't."
Some of them you've
read about in the papers.
"Others we hushed up."
Big spectacular crashes
- caused by terrific speed
- Oh. Mm.
or drunk driving
or some other form
of what I call near-insanity.
Stop the near-insanity!
But most people only
squeeze the law a little--
( siren wailing )
at stop signs,
in restricted speed zones,
and the like.
Little violations that
most people get away with
time after time,
maybe getting a ticket
- or a warning, like Frank, Jr. did,
- "Iowa P.D. Blue."
but without getting hurt.
But those little violations,
Ooh, wow!
those little chances
you take day by day,
that's where you start
playing roulette with your life.
You're taking a big gamble
with your life
( groaning )
when you violate a no passing
line on the road.
Whoa!
"My earlobes
won't stop growing."
You're taking a big chance
on the car in front
when you follow too
closely at highway speeds.
Maybe a man will do these things
a hundred times
- in perfect safety--
- Oh, the odds are pretty good.
squeeze the law--
and nothing happens.
But don't forget that other law,
- the law of averages.
- "I regret nothing."
Sooner or later,
it catches up with you.
Oh.
Now, this accident
was number one
for the driver involved.
The first one he'd ever had.
But it was his last one, too.
He took one little chance
too many.
Mother: Frank is taking
too many chances in his car.
"Mother, no."
Oh, he'll be all right.
Won't he, Hal?
He'll be all right if he takes to heart
what I told him about signs.
"Signs of Life"--
That's what stop signs and all
the other road signs really are.
Mm-hmm.
And missing one of them
as you drive along
- or just ignore it,
- "Anybody know this guy?"
that's one of those little things
that kills people.
"The world made sense
an hour ago."
Whenever there's
a hazard on the road,
there's usually a sign
to tell you about it,
- like a curve warning
- ( humming tune )
or a right of way sign,
narrow bridge,
- signals ahead, do not enter,
- I see. Mm-hmm.
- Doesn't mean a thing.
- no passing, and many others.
- "All-nude girls."
- "Whites only."
But for too many drivers
a stop sign,
- like this, for example,
- Is a target.
has no importance
unless they can see cars
crossing the road ahead
right now.
A school crossing sign
for some drivers
seems to mean little or nothing
- ( imitating ducklings )
- unless there are children
actually crossing the street
at that moment.
- As for railroad crossings,
- Forget 'em.
- ( train horn blows )
- some drivers act as if
the warning signs and tracks
don't even exist
unless there's a streamliner
passing by right in front of them.
Dirty Mary and Crazy Larry, no!
Hard as it is to believe,
there are many accidents
where the driver
ran past three warning signs
and straight into the side
of a moving train.
Ah, good riddance, I say.
...broad daylight, but it happens
even more often at night.
- That's when the warning sign,
- ( growls )
the signal, the crossbuck,
are really your signs of life.
"You see, son,
we all die alone and afraid."
The sign is still there,
but you have to be twice
as alert to see it.
- If you hadn't seen the signs,
- Boy, you haven't lived.
this train might come
as a surprise to you.
"The Sou-oul Train!"
( deep voice )
Thank you very much, Clarissa.
- Anytown, U.S.A.!
- Traffic signs and signals
that are so easy
to see in the daylight
become easier to miss
as the sun goes down.
Twilight is a dangerous time of day
when things are half visible,
- half in deepening shadow.
- "Half-naked."
Main Street at night becomes a maze
of lights and neon signs,
all competing with one another
to catch your eye.
So don't ever go to the city.
It's dirty.
- But where's the traffic signal?
- In your pants.
Oh, there it is,
almost lost against
the other lights beyond.
God, I had some times
in this town. Anyway...
Even the blinking red light
of the railroad wigwag
is hard to pick out sometimes.
Spilled my youth like cheap gin.
Anyway...
But night or day,
these are your signs of life,
whose purpose is to keep you alive.
Even though you
don't deserve it.
It's a strange thing,
but some people actually resent
- traffic signs and traffic laws.
- "We resent you being here."
Cramps their style.
They figure rules
are for the other fellow,
not for good drivers
like themselves.
- They're communists.
- Here's one like that.
Robert Bainbridge.
Bainbridge?
From Meridian High?
Oh, I know him. I ran against him
on the track team.
"Well, do you know him
like this?"
"No, no!
( screams )
"Dear God, who are you?
What are you?"
"I'm gonna go throw myself
in the thresher."
( sobbing )
I'm sorry, dear.
♪♪
- Yeah.
- Even with sensible,
safe-driving people
on a highway as smooth as silk,
♪ Kill the wabbit,
kill the wabbit ♪
with no traffic lights
and intersections,
- Wow!
- you might wonder,
"Where is the danger
we keep talking about?"
- Well, here's one danger-- fatigue.
- Kidnapping.
On long trips,
fatigue is a big hazard.
You should stop
at least once every hour.
- Get out, stretch your legs,
- Take some bennies.
- get those cobwebs out of your head.
- ( snorts, mutters )
Weariness slows down
your reactions,
and at 60 miles an hour
or better,
- you can't afford it.
- ( snoring, muttering )
"My life is a lie!"
Oh, no.
"Mm, don't love you, Martha."
( muttering )
- ( gasps )
- Whoops.
Now they're Ma and Pa Topper.
And here is still another danger--
lack of attention to the road.
Sure, it's an open highway.
Maybe there aren't many cars.
"Yeah, and I buried
the victims right over there.
- But it only takes two to tango.
- Right there."
Forty percent of all
expressway accidents
( imitates engine sputtering )
involve a car that has
already stopped--
Driven by this guy.
on the road, partway on,
or not far enough off.
- This is an invitation...
- "Look at that over there.
There's more of a... that thing."
( tires screeching )
( imitating Henry Kissinger )
Ach, Mr. President,
please watch where you're going.
Whoa! Almost ran over Kissinger.
I'm gonna have to go back.
Here is another hazard
of our superhighways
that we patrolmen see
all too often.
Women drivers.
Every time you have to
hit your brakes hard,
Saints cry.
ask yourself,
why weren't you ready
for the danger that
suddenly developed?
Forty percent of all accidents
are caused by women's hinders.
( trills tongue )
The first car suddenly
pulled out without looking.
It's always sudden, of course,
- and always surprising.
- But never dull.
A man who decides
at the last moment...
Grandma, no!
The entering car that fails
to yield the right of way.
The paid assassin
cruising through town.
Well, sure,
the other fellow's often wrong,
and if he causes a crash,
it's all his fault.
But you may be dead
just the same.
Would you please, please leave?
In a lot of accidents,
it's pretty hard to tell
just who is to blame,
isn't it, Hal?
- I ask you to talk?
- It's impossible to tell sometimes.
I want my din-din!
- ...where there's never a single doubt.
- What's that?
- At a railroad crossing.
- Yep.
- The train sure has the right of way.
- Yeah, whatever.
The railroad's been here
for almost four generations.
Every farm family
in these parts uses the railroad
to ship their crops.
- We all like to ride the train.
- I like to pretend I'm an engineer.
But why is it so many people
don't see the trains at the crossings?
It seems impossible that anyone
could fail to see
or hear a train in motion.
What train?
A locomotive is certainly
big enough,
and the train of cars behind it
may be as much as a mile long.
And yet, many people who have lived
- through a crossing accident will say
- Aah!
- "Where did the train come from?
- That's what they'll say.
"I never saw it
until it was right on top of me."
- Where did it come from?
- None of your beeswax.
Well, it came
on the rails.
It couldn't come
from anywhere else.
Duh.
But if you paid
no attention to the signs,
I hear it.
- didn't look and didn't listen,
- Then you deserve to die.
then for you
it came out of nowhere.
An approaching train
starts the signal
while it is still
some distance away.
Never try to guess how far away.
Don't guess at all.
- And don't be impatient.
- And don't get a haircut like that.
Because the train's coming,
and it can't stop.
Trains are blameless,
holy creatures.
- "I have no feelings for you!"
- "What?"
"This is a loveless relationship!
I want out!"
- "What?"
- "I'm repulsed by your touch!"
- "Let me out right here! I hate you!"
- ( imitating crossing bell )
- A signal in action means that
a condition of fatal danger exists
at this moment at this crossing.
Maybe the last train you waited for
was a slow freight
that took several minutes
to cross.
But the next one
may be a fast freight,
high-balling to the coast
on a tight schedule.
It has no time to stop for you
corn-shucking crackers.
Remember that many
freight trains today
are faster than passenger trains
of 15 years ago.
Oh, wow!
Many crossings have more
than one set of tracks,
each one a separate hazard.
- When you cross,
- Floss.
make sure all tracks are clear.
Don't trust anyone.
Turn your back on hope and love.
Yes, don't let a double track
double-cross you.
Ha, ha, ha. Little train joke.
"Stop, look, and listen,"
the crossbuck says.
- Stop, drop, and roll.
- All right, let's listen.
- Okay, now stop.
- As this train approaches,
let's see how close it comes
before we hear it.
I think it would go something...
like this.
Wait for it.
- Any moment now.
- And...
( gasps )
Oh! I'm the impish officer of death.
Now, where did
that train come from?
The station?
Where does any train come from?
- It comes on the rails, of course.
- Der-hay.
- And who gets killed at the crossing?
- We all do.
Someone who's crossed
that same track
at the same place
a thousand times before.
I'm making choo-choos
in my pants.
- One time is all it takes.
- Quit kissing up!
Send for help!
The cop won't leave!
It's Big Daddy's birthday!
I've got life in me, Big Daddy!
Please speak to Frank
about his driving.
It worries me.
Okay, I will.
I'll do it tonight.
This is the prequel
to "In Cold Blood." Clever.
I surrender, Hal.
I give up. What's the charge?
( laughs )
Manslaughter.
I'm just giving Alan some free advice
now that he's a licensed driver.
Boy, I remember that advice
you gave me the other day
at the stop sign.
- You keep it in mind.
- I will.
Dad, can I take the car
into town now?
Okay, Alan, go ahead.
But take it easy.
Oh, I'll be real careful.
Good-bye!
- He'll be all right.
- Look at the guy go.
Hey, maybe
we'd better go with him,
make sure he gets there all right.
- Okay. You can buy me a soda.
- Okay, fine.
- Good-bye, everybody.
- Bye.
Doesn't anybody do
any chores on this farm?
It's so funny.
So there went Alan
with his new driver's license,
and Frank and Betty right behind
on as nice a summer day
as you could wish for.
It's a good day to die.
"Hi, clouds. Hi, trees.
Say, you're a pretty
cute road sign. Hi."
You know, I've got a feeling
that one of these characters
is about to see their own intestines.
"Hey, look,
that's my brother in that truck.
What are the chances
of that happening? Hi, brother."
"Hey, the cop never
said anything about doing
intensely stupid things."
Never wave while driving.
Never look backwards
while driving forward.
Never, under any circumstances,
drive with your butt cheeks.
"My plan's working.
You will die."
"Keep going."
"Uh, back 'atcha."
( horn sounding )
"Can I have your room?"
Well, live and learn.
Say, nice butt.
"Toro, toro."
Ha, ha, I'm kidding.
"Well, I'd tuck you in,
but you're dead."
"Gee, lady, sorry
about your boyfriend."
"So, you want to have a drink
maybe at the bar car over-- Oh.
I suppose a train joke
is inappropriate."
Sorry about that."
"You know, son,
40% of all accidents..."
"Oh, shut up, will ya?"
"Would you identify this bucket
full of your brother?"
Why don't they look, Ralph?
Tell me.
Why don't they look?
"We're deep, Ernie."
No, I didn't go in.
Burying someone like young
Frank Dixon is too hard to take.
"Besides, I hate to shovel."
"Maybe I could just
slip over there for dessert."
- My place was out on the road.
- "Nah, might look bad."
Out on the road,
I could at least try
to keep other people from
killing themselves in their cars.
Oh, you're doing a great job.
So if the next car I stop
happens to be yours,
"Set a place for me
at your dinner table."
don't tell me you were
only speeding a little,
- only breaking the law a little,
- ( siren wails )
only doing something
a little bit wrong.
Save that for
somebody else, brother.
Oh, my God, he's snapped!
Because I've seen
too many little follies
He's a bad cop on the loose!
that end up with someone
a little bit dead.
Now I'm gonna grab
a little bit of lunch.
"Folks, we disavow
anything to do with that officer.
In fact, he was fired years ago."
"That's right.
Since his reign of terror,
we've instituted a strict policy.
"Any officer appearing unannounced
at a farmer's house
will be severely reprimanded."
Garganto-cop.
- ( theme plays )
- ( humming along )
♪ People are dead,
people are dying ♪
♪ Every day ♪
♪ They're dead, they're dead ♪
♪ Dead, dead, dead, dead ♪
♪ They're dead,
they're dead, they're dead ♪
♪ They're diddle-liddle li-ti-dead ♪
♪ They're diddle-liddle-
loop-de-dead, dead ♪
( all singing along )
Hi, I'm Trooper Tom Servo.
I've seen it all--
stared into
the gaping maw of death--
and I'm here to remind you
of the horror
that lurks everywhere.
No, don't get up.
You young people can
take things for granted,
such as your sandwiches.
Oh, I know you're just gonna eat
that sandwich a little bit,
with a little bit of mayo
and a little bit of hard salami.
( screaming )
Why don't they look?
Listen, brother, nearly 40-- uh, 40%
of all accidents represent, uh,
nearly half of all accidents.
But who cares?
Have fun with your lint trap.
Nothing will happen to you.
It'll happen to the other guy.
( screams )
- Why don't they--
- ( screams )
Why don't they look?
Well, say, hot plates are sure fun.
They're boss.
They're cool.
- Until...
- ( screams )
Why don't they...
Why do I even bother
with the brainless gibbons
who live in this stinking hole
of a town?
Well, I wash my hands of it,
brother!
- ( spits )
- ( gibbering )
Wow. Little guy really
gets into his roles, doesn't he?
Oh, hey.
Wonder what the Mads want.
Tom Servo: Oh, mad scientists.
Sure, you can have
a lot of fun with mad scientists,
until someone loses an eye.
Well, now that the local
has taken effect,
it's time for "Radar Secret Service,"
with full-blown
hypno helio static stasis.
Oh, Dr. Frankenkeister,
in your opinion,
would you say we're in for
a lot of standing around?
( laughing )
Great slabs of driving?
Hot gobs of talking?
Oh, yes. In short,
hypno helio static stasis.
Isn't that right,
Dr. Frankenkeister?
( bad accent )
Ja, ja. Sturm und drang. Ja.
( laughs, chortles )
♪♪
( humming tune )
"You may fire when ready,
Mr. Christian."
Available everywhere.
Hmm? Oh.
( chuckles )
That wasn't very good.
Rss! Rss! Rss!
"Gary Burghoff goes undercover."
That'd describe his career
for the past 10 years.
Look at all the dead cows
under that tower.
Ahh.
( theme plays )
Hmm. "Adele Jergens."
Hey, did you hear about
the Jergens worker?
No.
Fell into a vat and softened
himself to death.
( laughing )
That's my dad.
"Sid Melton."
Monkey boy.
Hey, he's back.
So where's the "radar" part?
- Yeah, come on.
- Yeah.
We can't wait for radar.
Ask us. We like to help.
( humming, whistling )
♪ Lou Asher is here ♪
This was one of the
highest-priced spec scripts
for that time, you know.
- Really?
- Yeah.
( vocalizing )
♪ I hear the robins sing ♪
"Yes, from the director
of 'I Accuse My Parents'
and 'Jungle Goddess'
comes 'Radar Secret Service.'
Let's watch."
Male narrator:
Radar: a magic word,
- born of a world conflict.
- War is good.
Modest in its beginning,
its only function was to warn
of the approach of an enemy.
A mere shadow across the screen,
and batteries of guns
were automatically set off,
messengers of death sent
screaming into the skies
- to fight off the intruder.
- Cool, huh?
This was radar... in war.
But with the peace came new discoveries
for this 20th century magic.
Stupid peace.
A lurking iceberg in the path
of an unsuspecting ocean liner
once spelled grave disaster
on the high seas.
It's a night to remember.
Now, thanks to radar,
a warning is flashed ahead
and the danger averted.
But can radar save
our stifling marriage?
...vast deposits of valuable minerals
buried deep in the earth
through the ages are being
uncovered continually
with the aid of radar.
Radar ferrets out clowns.
...were so needlessly wasted
scaling mountaintops
or crossing desert wastelands,
now, with the help of radar,
nature's innermost secrets
are being made known to man
with a minimum of effort.
The future of radar?
Who can foretell it.
This guy can't, that's for sure.
Already, images are being
flashed across wide spaces,
extending the range
of human vision beyond belief.
A prophesy of the unlimited
possibilities of radar,
Is found in the Bible.
particularly in the field
of scientific lie detection,
( exclaiming )
is the modest purpose of the picture
you are about to witness.
My life is a hollow lie.
- Well...
- Unfortunately, with radar,
we can now get
the Nashville Network.
Hey, "Powers That Be" is on.
I'll just diddle with the color here
a little bit.
Ah, forget it.
Let's see.
"Buy more radar."
Take a letter, Maria.
- Oh, good morning, Mr. Hamilton.
- Good morning, Tom.
- Nice pants.
- Any report on the supplies
that disappeared
from the Buell Air Base?
Our wylie beam picked up
something off the African coast.
"Wylie beam"?
The navy moved in
and nabbed a gunman
as he was trying
to smuggle equipment in.
Well, that's one case
we can write off.
How about the mineral deposits
reported in Alaska?
Got a negative reaction.
Low-grade duralite.
Well, at least we saved them
the cost of a crew of geologists.
( chuckles )
We saved them more than that.
( forced chuckling )
We increased the total fish catch
in this country
by thousands of tons.
I heard about that.
How'd it happen?
His face makes no sense.
One of our instruments
got a strange signal
- about 500 feet below the surface.
- Bob Vila.
Turned out to be
a large school of fish.
We turned the information over
to one of the fishing companies,
and now they're talking about
installing radar on all of their ships.
I've always maintained
there's no limit
to the possibilities of radar.
Now, where's
the damn donut cart?
- Has Bill Travis reported in?
- Yes, sir.
He thinks he has a lead
on the murder gun
in the Allen case.
We'd have an open-and-shut case
if he could dig up that gun.
"Your attention, please.
You will love radar.
Give yourselves to it freely."
( sobbing )
"Just get out. Get out."
"Oh, here's a lovely spot.
I'll get the picnic lunch."
"Oh, would you look at that?
Billie Joe McAllister's down there."
Whoever invented
this seeing-eye gadget
sure had it in for me.
We've been covering
this highway for 50 miles.
Not a sign of the gun.
Ah, quit griping.
If we don't find it here, we'll quit.
- Now you're talking.
- Come back tomorrow.
Look, we've got to find it.
See what's cooking.
Oh, my aching feet.
Have you tried radar
on your feet?
"It's amazing we can work together
after all that's happened,
eh, Gary?"
- Hey, look.
- I have water-weight gain.
This thing is picking up
a metallic reaction.
It could be the gun.
We know that Allen
made his getaway over this road.
Perfect spot to hide a gun,
if you ask me.
Keep working that thing
and let me know
when you hit the exact spot.
Work your evil magic,
radar thingy.
- Okay, say when.
- "Stella."
Move over. More, more.
Whoa. There you are.
That's it.
"Ted. Ted.
Ted, I'll take you to a restroom.
I thought you were over that."
"Hey, I found Judge Crater."
"Peace on Earth" was all it said.
"Blech! Want some?"
( fanfare plays )
Hey, I want to read that... Oh.
Hmm. Evidence that Christ
Himself invented radar.
What do you know?
Alien murder case, huh?
Okay, you can turn it now.
Turn it!
Headquarters is very pleased
with the help we gave
in the Allen case.
That's nice of them.
At least it shows
that with the improvements
we've made in the telemeter,
we can work hand in glove
with any branch of the government.
And should be a blow
to organized crime, too,
once they realize we can
keep a check on them.
- I hope so.
- Great. Super.
But there's still legwork
that can be eliminated.
That's for me.
I don't like legwork.
What do you expect to do?
Stay home in bed and have
radar do all the work?
That's not a bad idea.
Look, what we need
is more equipment.
"Stuff. Things."
A lot of what we do could be
done better by radar.
That's only a matter of time.
After all, we're infants
in this new field
of scientific detection.
We must crawl
before we can walk.
- "And now I need my binky."
- Don't mention "walk."
You can't blame me for dreaming.
No, not at all.
And a lot of those dreams
have come true
in the last few years,
like the image we get on our screen.
And to think that Dick Tracy used it
before it was invented.
And don't forget
Flash Gordon and Buck Rogers.
"And Lawrence Hilton-Jacobs
and Roddy McDowall
and Raoul Wallenberg and..."
"Any Farm Kid, U.S.A."
Oh, dinner at
the Homesick Restaurant.
Radar knows
what you want to order.
How'd she get into
that waitress outfit so fast?
Her head's a butter sculpture.
♪ There's a new girl in town ♪
♪ She's looking good! ♪
Anything special today?
- You!
- The White House surprise.
"Mm, what's your soup
du jour of the day?"
"We're out of Salisbury steak?"
"Material: 10 yards
of dotted Swiss. Hmm."
Mm, sounds interesting.
I'll order later.
"Well, I'm gonna cash out.
Blanche will be by
to take care of you."
"I could read that a thousand times."
♪ I get too hungry for dinner at 8:00 ♪
( humming )
Hey, it's the Boy Luck Club.
( chuckles )
Well, I enjoyed it.
( phone rings )
"Send up some gas juice.
You know, laugh water."
- Hello.
- "Yes, is Sid Melton there?"
Yeah. Yeah, fine.
I'll take it from here, honey.
- See you later.
- That was Honey West.
Violet's cooked up
another job for us.
"Hey, quit flashing
the neighbors back there."
We'll meet here in a couple hours.
I'll have the layout
worked out for us.
"We need something to
drab the room up."
I think I'll put on the feedbag.
I wish I was in love with a gal
that worked in a restaurant.
- Free eats.
- Yep. Aim high, Ted.
( chuckles )
♪♪
- Oh, boy.
- ( coughing )
Hey, Pill Box, want to
go to lunch with me?
Oh, no, doctor's orders.
I got to take my fresh-air
deep-breathing exercises.
I have to hurt you now.
- You know the window's closed.
- Huh?
I said, the window is closed.
- Oh, you got to open it?
- ( imitates rim shot )
"I'm gonna go have lunch
with Morey Amsterdam."
( clears throat )
Pardon me, is this booth taken?
Blackie.
Gee, I'm glad to see you.
"Did you bring that tip
you owe me?"
We're going on a job
this afternoon.
Yeah, I know.
What's the matter?
Aren't you happy?
If this pans out,
we'll have enough dough
to get married
and blow this town.
Do you mean that?
It's what I've been telling you
all the time.
One more good job,
and we can quit this racket.
- Looks like this is it.
- I'm so happy.
"Employees must wash tongues
before returning to work."
Wow!
- Okay.
- All: We're next.
- Uh, come in.
- "I'll have the French dip."
"I'll have the tongue sandwich,
if there's any left."
How'd you get this?
I told you about the plant
I had at the restaurant.
A lot of important people
eat there,
and eventually some of them talk.
Cheetah. Mm.
I'm beginning to wonder
how I ever got along without you.
And I was beginning to wonder
when you were going to
realize it.
No, no, no!
My grandparents are making out!
- ( ringing )
- Yes?
"So, how far did you get?
That leopard thing come off?"
Yes, I'll get on it right away.
"Got to go see if
my refrigerator's running."
- "Did you just call me?"
- What's up?
It's a truckload of
radioactivated U-238.
( gasping )
It's headed for
our local atomic plant.
U-238?
It's highly potential
ingredient for atomic energy.
"Or hot chocolate."
It can be used in commercial
and military use.
It'll revolutionize our power plant.
We have orders to keep it
under closest surveillance.
- "It's not better than radar, is it?"
- See if you can contact it.
Yes, sir.
He looks like a werewolf
in mid-transition.
Steven Tyler?
"Like Moses at the rock,
I had my first doubts
about radar that day."
"Oh, you've got the Radar
Secret Service screen saver."
"You kids turn off the radar.
It's a school night."
There it is.
Well, radar doesn't make the world
any more interesting, does it?
- Why, it doesn't have an escort.
- It's a closely guarded secret.
I think they're very wise
not calling attention
to the shipment.
- I still think it's too risky.
- "You don't deserve radar."
What's his bearing?
Jeez, the government
would collapse without this guy.
Highway 13, heading east.
Tell him to proceed
at once to the depot.
Yes, sir.
Look, supposing Static and I go out
and keep an eye on him
just in case.
Okay. Call me when
you get to the depot.
"And don't forget to use radar."
Notify the truck that a radar
car will meet them en route.
Yes, sir.
This guy is one of the best
interns they've ever had.
Calling OX-2.
Boy, just imagine this
on Omnimax.
- Wow.
- Ooh.
We'll watch for them
along the road.
I'll flash you as soon
as he picks us up.
Right.
I like that OX-2 guy.
He's real nice.
"What are you doing?
What's that thing?
What's that dial for?"
Boy, vintage cars were really
popular back then, huh?
There's the tunnel.
It should take them about 20 minutes
to reach the "dey-po."
Uh, "dee-po," sir.
"Here's the tunnel.
Should take us about 20 minutes
to reach the dey-po."
Keep in touch with them
till they get there.
Oh, you'd like that, wouldn't you?
OX-3. Calling OX-3.
Come in, OX-3.
Calling OX-3.
"That's probably for me.
It's my car."
- This is OX-3. Go ahead.
- "Hi, Huggy Bear."
Yes. sir.
"Uh-huh. No. No way.
She showed up with him?
- Wow!"
- Cut over to Highway 13.
( gasps )
It's the Naegele capers!
It's certainly taking that truck
a long time
to get through that tunnel.
Make it go faster.
- Ah, wow.
- Here it comes now.
"I can see that. I'm looking at it.
I invented radar."
( goofy laugh )
"Tell me about the rabbits again.
Oh, it can wait."
( humming along to soundtrack )
Why is he turning off
that highway?
"Radar can't look
into their hearts, sir."
He's disobeying orders.
Try to get through to him.
Tell him to get back
on the highway.
Yes, sir.
- ( goofy vocalization )
- OX-2, come in.
- Calling OX-2. Come in.
- "You go ahead."
It's no use. His set
must be fouled up.
"I'm gonna go on break."
Well, we're losing him now.
He's... He's getting out of our beam.
Send out an alert.
Notify Bill of his change of direction.
Keep trying to get him
back on the screen.
Yes, sir. OX-3.
Come in, OX-3.
"I have a name,
you know. It's Dave."
This is OX-3. Go ahead.
"The calls are coming
from inside the car!"
"Dirt road five miles
along Highway 13."
Okay. Step on it.
You're not that funny.
- ( all gasp )
- Wow!
Incredible!
"A Very Walton Radar Christmas."
"The Joads Pull a Heist."
That is a full acre of car there.
Yep.
That damned Swatch.
♪ Ride ♪
♪ Riding like the demon ♪
♪ That drives your dreams ♪
"Hardcastle and McCormick."
"Hey, pull over.
Gotta hang out the radar dish,
if you know what I mean."
"When AAA was controlled
by the mob."
( hysterically imitating
dramatic soundtrack )
- "Oh, you're here."
- You have any trouble?
They never knew what hit 'em.
- You didn't knock them off?
- Of course not.
They're just out cold.
Well, dump 'em and head for the barn.
I'll meet you there.
All this to plan a family reunion.
"Here, I'll drive.
Oh, I'm the only one."
"Let's see. Dead body, dead...
Where did I put that thing?
Oh, there it is."
( imitating engine )
"Damn you, Duke boys!"
( gibbering like
Roscoe P. Coltrane )
The music bespeaks tension,
yet I feel so empty.
"Chrome golf balls on sale now."
That must be it.
Turn in there.
"You said this wouldn't be fun."
"Colander Warehouse.
All we do is colanders,
and we do them right."
"Oh, I'll carry you."
♪ Oh, those Golden Grahams,
oh, those Golden Grahams ♪
Only radar knows
what the hell is going on.
That vehicle is so close
to being an unmarked car.
"I only do these capers
for the scenery."
"My life is one big to-do list."
- "The melon squad is in hot pursuit."
- Let's go, Blackie!
It's not "Blackie,"
It's "African-Americanie."
"Whoa! Whoa! Okay, I'll walk!"
"And the goiter-mobile is there."
"Hi. Listen, I've got some news.
"I came to tell you that
we were maybe gonna-- Hey!"
Take care of the boys.
"Ah, we're done."
"How Green Was My Radar?"
"Oh, the Johnsons are early."
"Oh, my atrizine representative."
( goofy gibbering )
You know, maybe a parking ramp
way out there wasn't a good idea.
♪♪
What's the matter
with "Mr. Roboto"?
Nothing's the matter with it.
- Hey! Here he comes!
- ♪ You don't love me ♪
Hey, what's going on?
What is all this?
- ( exclaiming )
- Well, Mike, we know
the hypno helio static stasis
might be getting to you, so we--
And we know that you had to miss
your 10-year high school reunion,
so we decided to have one for you.
Yeah. We found your yearbook,
so we're all set
to simulate the actual
reunion experience.
Wow, that's-that's great.
Thanks.
- I'm really excited.
- That's great.
Put your nametag on,
there, Mike, and welcome to
the Baribou High School
class of '83 reunion
here at the Budget Hotel
Regency Room off County Trunk D!
- ( exclaims )
- Oh! Oh!
Oh! Oh, Jeez! Oh!
Nelson? Mike Nelson?
Buddy! Nelson, man!
What's going on, man?
Man, I envy you, Nelson.
You made it.
You're got out of this town, man.
Wow! I married Pam,
just like everybody said I would.
It's okay, I guess.
Hey, I never see you down
at the Rendezvous anymore, man.
That's 'cause I don't live
around here anymore.
Yeah, that's probably it.
Man, I envy you, Nelson.
You made it.
You got out of this town, man.
- Mike?
- Oh, boy.
Mike Nelson! Remember me?
Janine. Janine LaFond.
Right, how you doing,
Janine LaFond?
Oh, yeah, except for now,
it's Janine LaFond-Spike.
How are you?
I'm good.
It's good to see you again.
Hey, how come you never
asked me out, huh?
I just always thought
you were totally stuck-up.
Oh, hey, I'd better go call the sitter.
She's got her hands full with those
nine rugrats and everything.
- See ya!
- Yeah, right.
Nine kids in 10 year--
Hi, Mike.
Hi, um, uh, uh, uh...
- Guess.
- Um...
Rick. How you doing, Rick?
- Good to see you.
- No.
I sat three seats behind you
and four back
in Health and Family Living.
It's John. How are you, John?
- No.
- Hey, everybody. Brenda again.
Okay, here is the answer
to the trivia question.
Cindy Gannett called her car
"Land Yacht."
Okay. Now we're gonna
get going with the music.
Here's Impaler!
( exclaiming )
It's Jim.
No, I can't, 'cause...
I've got to get some punch,
and it's movie sign!
( chuckling )
Oh, fun, huh?
"Well, as long as we're all here,
let's draw names for Christmas."
Where's Blackie?
Squad car showed up, and I
had to get away in a hurry.
He couldn't make it.
Do you think
they picked him up?
Must have.
That's a bad break for him,
but a good break for us.
How do you figure that?
Won't have to cut
the melon so thin.
They've got melons.
Yeah, but suppose they start
sweating him and he sings?
Don't worry about him singing.
He's crazy about Marge,
and he wouldn't want
anything to happen to her.
Hey, Sid Melton.
I'll meet you later
at the apartment.
Okay.
"What page do
our lines begin on?"
They grabbed off one of my men,
but we got the truck
hidden in a barn.
When do you want to pick it up?
You make it sound so easy.
- Well, what's wrong with it?
- The radar patrol.
Where do you think
those cops came from?
You're gonna have it
halfway across the ocean
before they get wise.
Michael is right.
They'd grab you the minute
you made a move.
They've got
the whole town covered.
Peggy Lee runs the mob.
Looks like I'm outnumbered
around here.
Well, what do you think
we ought to do?
Change pants?
My first suggestion is to
get rid of that radar truck.
- Blasphemer!
- He must die.
And then what?
I have a yacht about
six miles up the river.
- It's called Monkey Business.
- That's interesting.
You can reach it from an old pier
about 20 miles out of town
on the river road.
We'll need some help
to get it aboard ship.
Just get it near that pier.
My boys will take care of the rest.
And then I get paid, huh?
What's the matter?
Don't you trust me?
This is one of those important
moments in any relationship.
I'd better not answer that.
Look, we got it halfway to you.
I want half the dough now.
"Well, here.
Dan Fogelberg tickets."
"Got to move my condoms.
Surprised I have any left."
We're stepping out tonight, sugar.
I'm sorry.
I promised Michael I'd...
I'll pick you up about 8:00, my dear.
"It's not the radar,
it's the size of the amplitude,
if you know what I mean."
"That's okay. I don't care."
"And never darken
my carpets again!"
Remember me?
I'm your boyfriend, Mickey Moran.
"Oh, that's right.
I'm terrible with names."
I don't like the way
this deal is turning out.
- You like his money, don't you?
- Well, sure.
- What do you like about him?
- He's the contact we need.
I'm just as anxious as you
to get this job over with
so we can all be paid off.
Uh, he's on fire.
Your jealousy is
going to ruin everything.
Now, look, baby,
when this job is over,
you figure on combing lover boy
out of your hair
with a fine-toothed comb.
"I haven't combed my hair in 13 years.
You know that."
Her hair is soft-serve.
They should put that curl on it.
"I'm not drinking. Nope."
- You get anything out of him?
- ( both exclaim )
No, not a peep.
I'm having them check the files
for a possible lead.
- He may have a record.
- ( whistles )
"No waffles!"
- Anybody we know?
- What? Who?
No, no. It's just a picture
that I got out
of his little black book.
- Whose little black book?
- "Bob Packwood's."
The guy we picked up.
The fellow on the road.
Where did you get it?
I think he dropped it.
I picked it up off of the floor.
You picked it up off the floor?
"That's my wife, you bastard."
This may be the answer
to our problem.
What is it?
- "A coupon for yams."
- Probably one of his girlfriends.
"Can I help you?
Smoking or non?"
We might be able to learn
a lot from her.
- "Busing tables..."
- Who couldn't?
Check every restaurant in town.
It shouldn't be tough
running her down.
"Pretty run down already."
( chuckles )
But I kid.
- ♪ Where are you going? ♪
- ♪ I don't know ♪
- ♪ How you gonna get there? ♪
- ♪ I ain't certain ♪
♪ All I know is that I'm on my way ♪
"No, sir.
I never seen her."
Well, why don't they try
using that radar
they're always bragging about?
"Get out of here,
you filthy little man."
"I thought they served fun
at Shakey's."
"That's the oddest thing
anyone's ever showed me."
Boy, she can really
hold a smile for a long time.
- It's a picture.
- Oh.
"The layout of this place..."
"Nice salad bar."
"Look, would you just
bring me my meat loaf?"
"Meat?"
"I've got a coupon here."
"All right. Two for one."
"Get over there.
Stake out the dessert tray."
♪ Are you happy in your work ♪
( humming )
"Butter. Mm."
Those two haven't talked
in years, have they?
They're from the Midwest.
"We're out of everything
except orange juice."
I know what I want.
If it isn't on the menu,
we're not serving it.
"Oh, aren't there specials
sometimes on the blackboard?"
- I didn't catch your name.
- I didn't throw it.
- Wait here. I'll be right back.
- "Please don't eat the daisies."
"I gotta call this order
into the kitchen."
"Well, I have...
"Well, I found my dream restaurant.
"I give them two Michelin
stars for service,
"although the duck
a l'orange was a little tough.
Hey, I haven't eaten yet."
( chuckles )
"I stole the butter mints."
- ( ringing )
- ( humming tune )
Yeah?
- Hello, let me speak to Blackie.
- This is Marge.
- Blackie?
- She's large.
- "No, it's Marge."
- Oh, you mean he's in jail.
I'll call you back later.
"I always forget he goes
to jail on Tuesdays."
"Oh, stiffed again."
- That was Marge.
- "She's large."
Says there's a guy
at the restaurant
claims he's a friend of Blackie's.
What'd he want?
She didn't say.
She just hung up.
- "She just hung up."
- Why? Anything wrong?
- That hat.
- Maybe and maybe not.
The cops could've got
a line on us through Blackie.
The sooner we unload the stuff
and get our dough,
the better I'll like it.
What's this Michael guy
stalling around for, anyway?
I don't know.
It could be business,
- and then again it could be...
- Lila.
Yeah, and I don't like it.
I'll see if I can't get some action.
Stick around.
Don't say bye or anything.
- Hey, boss.
- ( all groaning )
- You going past Thrifty's Drugstore?
- You sick again?
Oh, am I sick. I feel terrible.
My head hurts,
my pulse is 140, net,
my low blood pressure
is with hypertension,
and my temperature is
by the arrow, Fahrenheit,
and my stomach refuses
to recognize the rest of me.
And you ask me, am I sick?
All right, what do you
want me to get you?
- Bubble gum.
- ( weak chuckle )
( imitating Johnny Carson )
You know, Ed,
that was a long way
for a little bit.
After you get the material
out of the country,
what are you planning to do?
"Oh, make a sarong or a blouse.
Maybe a skirt."
First, we haven't got
the stuff out of the country.
Second, you ask
too many questions.
"What do you mean by that?"
I'm sorry, Michael.
Is everything still as we planned?
We've talked this over several times.
Oh, man, they did this scene
on "Don Adams' Screen Test."
Moran phoned and said
they got rid of the truck.
He ought to be here any minute.
I don't want him to find me here.
Phone me as soon as
you get rid of him.
- Fold you?
- ( doorbell buzzes )
"Oh, it's probably that
nosy Mrs. Kravitz."
"Welcome.
Welcome to the House of Mafia."
Mm. Laura Ashley.
Very homey.
Well, did you have any trouble
getting rid of the truck?
Of course not.
If I hadn't listened to lover boy,
we could've unloaded the truck
at the same time
and got paid off.
He's just as anxious as you
to get his hands on that material.
I hope for his sake that's all
he wants to get his hands on.
"Help yourself to my booze."
Where did he say that yacht was?
About six miles up the river.
Tell Michael when you see him
there'll be a small load
on the way to his boat
in a couple of hours.
If we get through,
we'll have the rest there by tonight.
- Are you out of your mind?
- ( hysterical gibbering )
There's no use
ruining everything.
We didn't have any trouble hijacking
the truck in the first place.
I still say let Michael
do the thinking on this job.
He's not thinking fast enough for me.
He's stalling.
I want action.
I'm gonna get it.
Surprise!
Benson, I got a problem.
I don't remember
whether the doctor
told me to take five pills at 8:00
or eight pills at 5:00.
Why don't you play safe
and take 13?
- Oh, no. I'm superstitious.
- ( doorbell buzzing )
He's this close to
being Casey Kasem.
Thirteen pills. I'll rattle.
His stuff is just over my head.
I don't know.
Sophisticated.
Hiya, boss.
You got my bubble gum?
( all chuckling )
Kill him.
- How'd you make out?
- "Used my tongue."
We'll start moving those carts
to the boat right away.
- What's the layout?
- If we get through,
we'll move the rest tonight
and get paid off.
I don't know.
I think we're sticking our necks out.
"Sounds like they're
sticking their necks out in there."
"After a 14-hour shift,
I love to wear spike heels."
"Good morning, ma'am.
Have you ever tried Mary Kay?
Good morning, ma'am.
I'd like to introduce you
to Mary Kay's line of--"
"Get out of the bushes, Josh."
"Yeah, this is gonna be...
Ah, nothing means
anything to me anymore."
- What do you want?
- "A poodle."
- I just left Blackie.
- He's all right, ain't he?
Sure, he's all right,
but what are you gonna
do about him?
Benson, see that he gets
some spending money.
- Sure.
- Forget that.
What are you gonna do
about springing him?
Well, I suppose I could
call up my friend the D.A.
and ask him to release him.
I need him on another job.
She looks like one of
Donald Duck's nephews.
Listen, Margie,
we'll spring your boyfriend
when we're ready and not before.
Well, it'd better be soon.
- Is that a threat?
- Maybe.
Well, don't try anything foolish.
You might get hurt.
Go see Michael.
He's got all the dough.
- Come on.
- "I got to go shave
above and below
my mustache."
She's kind of pillowy, isn't she?
"Oh, hi, guys.
How's the caper going?"
We got to start using both doors.
"Oh, I want them to like me.
Maybe I should just
introduce myself."
Hey, Freddy Fender.
- "Auto" Preminger.
- James Car-ville.
- Harrison Ford.
- 'Cause they're cars.
There's something cooking.
They were in an awful hurry
when they drove away.
Didn't you follow them?
No, I got hemmed in
by a couple of cars,
and by the time I worked
my way out, they were gone.
- "Well, gee, Bob..."
- "Howard!"
They haven't got a chance.
The moment they make a move,
I'll know it.
Suppose we start cruising.
You can signal us
if anything turns up.
Right.
Doesn't he ever leave the office?
"You have to carry
your Hummels everywhere?"
We're going to head north.
Be back in a couple of hours
for another load.
Meanwhile, you men lay low.
"I'm gonna till the back 40.
You guys start disking."
Farming stuff, right?
"Okay, I'll drive to Racine,
then you take over after Tomah."
You know, I grew up
in a house smaller than that car.
On the farm?
♪ On the days we sweated ♪
♪ Out on the street ♪
♪ On a last-chance... ♪
You know, the small
gangster farmers
are just a thing of the past.
Hey, Thelma and Luigi.
Oh, there goes the knee.
"No, I will not
kiss you for a dollar."
As a matter of fact,
he does own the road.
"Man, I thought Radio Shack
stood for quality."
It stands for "failing mall."
That's it.
It's that sedan heading north,
license...
- "FOXY 1."
- 031768.
Send out an alert.
Then try and get ahold of Bill.
Yes, sir.
"Oh, good.
Back to 'Empty Nest'."
I can't figure out how Marge
fits into this picture.
"Move over."
All we know for sure is that
she's Blackie's girlfriend.
I hope for her sake
she's not in any deeper in this.
Sure looks like a nice kid.
OX-3. Calling OX-3.
This is OX-3.
Go ahead.
"Oh, hi, chief. What?
I'm wearing a fedora. Why?"
River highway heading north.
License number 03768?
- Check.
- Great license number.
♪ Head out on the highway ♪
( vocalizing hokey beat )
♪ Looking for adventure ♪
"Duplicate shots with radar.
Yes, thanks to radar,
we've only needed
to shoot three scenes."
"I can't grow a mustache."
"That's right.
Kettledrums. All sizes.
Kettledrums. Get them here."
That looks like 'em there.
"Uh, the Chevy with
the rice cooker on its roof
is following us again."
♪ Oh, those Golden Grahams ♪
This looks like where
they filmed a bunch
of "Barnaby Jones" episodes.
Speaking of "Barnaby Jones,"
did Mr. Woodman
ever have Kotter as a student?
Yeah. That's why they called it
"Welcome Back, Kotter."
Oh, that's it. Oh.
Was Juan Epstein
Puerto Rican or Jewish?
He was both.
That was his whole gig.
I get it now.
That's the whole gag of Epstein.
Come on.
Hence the name "Juan."
"Juan Epstein."
Hmm. Thank you.
You're welcome.
You know, this movie--
biggest September opening in history.
Even beat out "Under Siege."
- Get out.
- No, I won't.
- Get out!
- No!
Keep an eye on this thing.
I'll see if I can spot the men.
All right.
♪ Oh, those Golden Grahams ♪
"Thanks to radar,
the scene promptly ends."
"Flash!
Footage used over and over.
"Radar racked by scandal.
"Exclusive photos
of early-morning raid.
"See the shaken radar
moments after the charges
of footage duplication."
- Cute.
- Thank you.
That really was quite nice.
I liked it, too.
- Quick little bit, wasn't it?
- Yeah.
We checked on
the ownership of that car.
Stolen about a week ago.
They'll be very leery
about moving
any of that
material after this.
I don't think I'm gonna
wait for them to move.
They called it Moby Car.
"I see the belly
of the great white car."
- Thanks for the lift.
- Is Moran up there?
I don't know,
but I'm supposed to meet him here.
"I resent you. Good night."
"Man, I'm chafing like a bear.
These Italian bun-huggers
give me no room at all."
"Oh, message for me.
'Top boss needs to talk...'
I never got this message!"
Come in. I want to talk to you.
"Come in?
How much more in could I be?"
I don't remember having
a date with you.
"I must've been drunk."
You will.
- How'd you get in here?
- Same way you did.
- "Levitation."
- Well, what do you want?
"Same thing you want."
I'd like to ask you
a couple of questions.
It's about that car
that was abandoned awhile back.
What's that got to do with me?
You look like one of the boys
that got away.
- Lots of guys look like me.
- "You should see my mother."
Sorry. You'll have to
try a new attack.
That's a good suggestion.
Let's go down to headquarters.
It's a bum rap, copper.
"I need a bigger steering wheel."
- Mickey.
- "I like your cakes.
I mean, your desserts.
Oh, never mind."
- "Here. I've got your coleslaw."
- What are you doing here?
- I just drove up with Benson.
- Is he up there?
Yeah. How about Blackie?
Now, how about him?
"Oh, outwitted again."
♪♪
Mind if I call my attorney?
Sure. Go right ahead.
"Hello. Law offices?"
- "I'm dull."
- "No, I'm way duller."
"Okay, name my character."
"Uh, jeez. Uh, uh-- I can't!"
"See? Which one of us
is the good guy?"
"I don't know,
I don't know. Who am I?"
Ah, the Martin and Lewis
breakup was so sad.
( imitating Jerry Lewis )
"Oh, with the punch and the..."
"Take it there."
"Sparky?
Sparky, bad dog! No!"
He was checking up
on that car we ditched.
They sure didn't waste any time.
"My gun. Gimme. Mine."
Not here.
We'll take him down the back way.
"Okay, let's do that
'Weekend at Bernie's' routine."
- ( footsteps )
- Let's get out of here.
♪ Frere Jacques dormez-- ♪
Merde!
( screaming )
Oh, there's a dead man!
It's all right, Myrtle.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you!
The director's mistress,
ladies and gentlemen.
The director's mistress.
Oh, good guy, bad guy?
Good guy or bad guy?
I don't... which...
"Don't say it.
I know. I'm blurry."
( groaning )
"Hey, where are my fries?"
He must've got a bad clown burger.
What'd you use, a sledgehammer?
Hey, wait a minute.
I didn't do it.
No, I don't think you're the type.
Anyway, if you had,
you wouldn't have stuck around
to play nursemaid.
You hurt bad?
- I'll live.
- He's demonic.
Hey, wait a minute.
You're Blackie's girl, aren't you?
That's no crime.
- No.
- "Not in a strictly Cartesian sense."
It's a crime the way
your friends
are letting him
take the rap for them.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
- We don't either.
- Put it this way.
With Blackie in jail,
they don't have to
cut him in on the payoff.
You don't call that
playing it smart, do you?
What do you want me
to do about it?
"Dress as a leopard
and sing 'La traviata'."
You help us, we'll help Blackie.
Tell us who's behind this.
"You scratch my head,
I'll wash yours."
You mean, if I talk,
you'll release him?
I can't make any promises,
but we'll do all we can.
"I'll have to run it
by the sales manager."
Look, if you think your friends
are gonna be bighearted
and help Blackie,
you're wasting your time.
Let me think it over, I said.
Then, just when I thought
I had the situation under control,
- the roof fell in.
- "'Boom,' it went."
When I came to, there was
Blackie's girlfriend looking at me.
What a wonderful way
to wake up.
Shut up.
I tried to get her to talk,
even promised to go easy
on Blackie if she did.
No soap. I think
she's softening, though.
I hope so, for her sake.
"Hi, sugar lumps."
"Hi, lamby legs."
Wasn't such a good idea after all.
It's too bad they didn't get
Mickey, too.
- Has he been around?
- Not yet.
"Good Jumble today."
I'm getting a little jittery
about the whole thing myself.
They seem to know
every move we make.
( gasping ) Radar!
Do you know where
to reach Moran?
He must be at the barn.
Get him on the phone
and have him come over.
I've got an idea I think might work.
I wonder if she ever
talks into the statue by accident.
Why don't you shut up?
I'm sick of listening to you.
Always complaining.
Why, you're probably
healthier than I am.
I can't stand it anymore.
This is the last straw.
This joint is killing me.
I'm getting out.
I'm leaving...
- to get a drink of water.
- ( weak chuckling )
Thank you, Sid.
Was it anything important?
Lila wants to talk over something
lover boy's dreamed up.
Why don't we turn over
the stuff to him right here
and get the rest of our dough?
The longer we hold on to it,
the hotter it gets.
I tried to sell him on that idea,
but he won't hold still.
He wants to load it on the yacht.
You don't suppose he's trying
to pull a fast one on us, do you?
Hey, that's it. He might try
to double-cross us, huh?
- Keep your shirt on.
- Yeah, please.
I'll see what's cooking.
"Sure. Swell. Palooka.
Wise guy, huh?"
It looks like we can't do a thing
until they move
some more of the material.
That's right. Our beams
are all transverse
on a horizontal plane.
"Uh, sir, your fly's..."
Anything would have to cross
in front of these beams first
- "Uh, sir, your..."
- before we get a reaction.
But they may hole up for months.
Look, if we put
our equipment up high,
we can spot them
in no time, couldn't we?
You mean fly over \the city
in a plane?
- Exactly.
- "No, a duck."
Even if you could throttle down
to a hundred miles an hour,
I'm afraid that'd be too fast
for our outfit to pick up anything.
It doesn't have to be a plane.
No, how about a balloon?
Sure, or a blimp or a helicopter.
Anything that'll float
right over the rooftops.
And beam down on
the hidden material?
That's right.
I'll get busy on it right away.
"See? Here I am.
Busy, busy, busy."
Get me the airfield.
Man, she must get a keg
of Cutty Sark every weekend.
Is that unusual?
Pretty close call, eh, Moran?
I can't understand how
they could spot me so quickly.
( all whispering )
Radar! Radar!
We can't make a move
without ringing a bell.
- That's exactly what I have in mind.
- Ding, ding, ding.
Say we move another load
of the material.
They send out an alert,
and the chase is on.
Wait a minute.
We just tried that deal.
Didn't pan out so good.
Why don't you wait till Michael
tells you what he has in mind.
"Oh, Michael this, Michael that.
Why don't you just marry him?"
- I'm listening.
- As I started to say,
we load a couple
of cartons into a car
and start it across town,
but in the opposite direction.
"'Budget Park and Ride.'
This is ridiculous!"
They're on the moon.
- "Wash me."
- ( chuckling )
♪ And on this farm he had a chick ♪
♪ The swingin'-est chick I know ♪
"Waldo Pepper, you in there?"
- Get any action?
- ( scoffs ) In this movie?
Yeah, we're loading
the stuff right now.
Who's loading
what stuff right now?
Quit squawking.
I'll tell you about it later.
Hey, Gus, Joe, come here.
- These are the good guys, right?
- I don't know.
Get a couple small cartons
off the back of the truck
and load them
in the turtleback of my car.
Okay, boss.
I bet they're pushing
counterfeit blue jeans.
We're gonna put
some of the stuff in the car
to use as a decoy to keep
the radar patrol off our tail.
- "Oh, like a duck, sir."
- If we can get 'em on our tail.
We're not gonna be in the car.
We're gonna be in the truck
with the rest of the stuff
on the way to the yacht.
- You get it?
- Who is gonna be in the car?
"Ric Ocasek."
"Girl Scout cookie time."
"Each box contains
a piece of Sid Melton."
So where are we--
In the trunk? We're in the thing?
- In the yacht.
- They'll never be caught... alive.
( maniacal laughter )
Hey, don't cut away so fast.
"Barely room for
Mr. Hoffa in there."
Now, here's the dope.
"Take it to Kurt Cobain's house."
- Get him! Get him!
- Might be able to...
Just take it easy
and don't drive fast.
Get back as fast as you can.
Key's in the car.
Right.
♪ This is a thing
you've never known before ♪
- Servo!
- ♪ It's called-- ♪ Aah!
- Aah!
- Hey.
Say, Crow and I did
a little project we want to do
when we get back down to Earth,
and we were wondering...
What you got?
A little project here?
Well, bring it on in here,
you little scamps.
Let me have a look at it.
Well, say.
It's the Quinn Martin Nature Preserve.
It's a place where old Quinn Martin
character actors will go
to roam free in their natural habitat.
What the hell?
Yeah. Enter Q.M.N.P. here,
and pay a nominal fee
to ticket taker Anthony Zerbe.
As you drive on,
the rolling hills are dotted
with the fauna of early Quinn Martin
success, The Untouchables.
Here, Robert Stack
playfully pulls a muskrat
from the mouth
of fellow G-man Jerry Paris,
who wrestles with
alpha male Lloyd Nolan.
As you drive on,
you might surprise,
oh, Efram Zimbalist, Jr.
munching contentedly
at the eucalyptus leaves
that were planted
especially for him.
Idle your car down now,
'cause you're likely
to rile Michael Douglas
or get between
Karl Malden and his cubs
( growls ) here on the Plains
of San Francisco, or...
- Can I interrupt you right here?
- Sure.
Is there gonna be
a "Harry O" exhibit?
Well, that's a good question,
but "Harry O" has not
been classified
as a Quinn Martin production.
- Hmm. All right. Go on.
- Right.
In the heat of the midday sun,
many Q members
take refuge at the David Janssen
watering hole.
This becomes a place
of great activity,
and inter-series mingling
is not uncommon.
You could see, oh, Roy Thinnes
picking nits off Buddy Ebsen
or Lee Meriwether perched
on the gargantuan back
of William Conrad.
- Oh, boy.
- Wait a minute.
There's a commotion
in the deep grass.
- It's the Quinn Martin guest stars.
- ( growling )
Bradford Dillman is feasting
on the carcass of Pat Hingle...
- Guys. Guys.
- when it's wrested from his jaws
and torn to shreds
by James Franciscus.
- The fur flies until Ken Howard...
- Guys, guys, guys!
- Crow! Mike! Guys!
- What?
- What's happened to you?
- What do you mean?
I mean, Ken Howard,
Pat Hingle, nits?
Good Lord,
it's the helio hypno static stasis!
It's working on you!
- Servo, you may be right.
- I am right.
You may have something
there, Servo.
Buddy Ebsen would never allow
Roy Thinnes to pick \nits off him.
Oh, Crow!
We'll be right back
while I deprogram these two.
Crow!
♪♪
Better? Good.
What? A helio-copter aerial plane.
"Oh! Did you have to bring
your walker up here?"
- Bill standing by?
- Yes, sir.
See if you can contact that plane.
"Oh, sir, may I suggest
a sponge bath or something?"
♪ On the road again ♪
( humming tune )
"Gee, it was just a joke.
I'm sure your mother's very nice.
I mean, she's old, but..."
I just got it.
This must be where
the hypno helio static stasis
really kicks in.
It's the detector gauge.
Some radar equipment
just crossed the beam.
Run it down.
Notify Bill immediately.
All: Radar!
That's right!
Radar makes a big return!
We're back on track with radar!
- I missed radar.
- I love radar.
Not a wide variety
of car colors back then.
That's it. The limousine.
It's right on the beam.
Contact Bill and give him
the bearing of the car.
Then get hold of the helicopter
and tell him to keep
cruising over town.
- Yes, sir.
- "And call my wife.
She's remarried since
we last talked."
OX-3. OX-3.
Calling OX-3.
These are the good guys.
Feel their goodness
wash all over you.
"Huh? Hugh Jass?
Just a minute. I'll check."
Car heading east, license 4M263.
Bingo.
Check.
What's up?
Spotted a car with some more
of that stolen material.
Chintz.
Sure didn't wait long
to try again.
Head for the river road.
♪ Almost heaven, West Virginia ♪
Come on, sing with me!
♪ Blue Ridge Mountain ♪
That's some right pretty country.
"Bobbers.
Red and white plastic bobbers.
They float. Use them."
He's gaining on them.
- "Stop that!"
- What's wrong with that wheel?
I don't know.
There's something wrong
with the steering wheel.
It's Universal's
crazy new radar ride.
What's wrong with that guy?
I don't know,
but if he doesn't watch out,
he's gonna lose control
of that car.
"Oh, it's okay. It's okay.
Wait a minute. There."
- Do something!
- I can't!
Wow. Must be Yeltsin
driving that car.
There he goes.
Hey, that's a Model A!
Different movie!
"Acorn squash-- Make
a delicious winter soup."
"Van de Graaff generators.
Practice science
in your own home."
"But there was no monster."
"What is this thing?
Am I helping at all?"
They've had time enough.
Let's go.
"Let's synchronize our ties."
Either these are tiny gangsters,
or that's a huge car.
♪ Tiny gangster ♪
You know, every single scene
is done...
- ♪ In cars ♪
- ( humming "Cars" )
"In the future,
you will drive to work and play
"in huge loaves of hollowed-out bread.
Miracle Teflon Brewer's Yeast
makes it possible."
So it was "Boom Boom" Washington...
What did the "Boom Boom"
stand for?
He played bass.
The problem is,
there was too much radar early.
Now there's radar.
I don't care.
These people have no idea
of the drama unfolding
in their backyards.
"I know."
Ooh, God, for a Stinger right now.
The drink or the missile?
Well, either one.
It's a young
Hubert Humphrey piloting.
"I don't even know what
we're looking for anymore!"
OX-Q, just spotted
a truck with materials.
It's the helicopter.
They've spotted another
load of material.
Contact Bill
and give him the bearing.
- Yes, sir.
- Oh, good.
Let's watch the same scene
from a different angle.
Keep in line with that truck.
Oh, is this what they mean
by fall colors?
Gray and gray?
All the leaves are gray.
And the sky is..
OX-3. Calling OX-3.
"I want to get it.
You always get it."
Calling OX-3.
"No. Oysters, I think."
Hal, that's fine. I'll have them
in my hip pocket in no time.
There's another car heading
up the river road.
We'll notify the police
about the wreck on the way.
Say, this may be a decoy
to throw us off the track.
Smart boy. Let's go.
"You really think I'm smart?
Really?"
"We now return to Riptide."
I almost killed myself
when that was canceled.
Really?
This is so bad,
I wish it was "Air America."
Yuck.
"You want to buy
a house together?"
Why not just drive
if you're gonna fly that low?
"Hi. I'm new to the film."
"Beach balls.
Get your beach balls.
Throw them back and forth
on the beach."
"How many hats do you own?"
Oh, oh, they're using
the super-secret quiet helicopter
to sneak up on the bad guys.
If I'm not mistaken,
they might have a cloaking
device on that helicopter.
"Welcome to Action Valley Ranch."
OX-Q. OX-Q.
Truck just turned off
into Bouquet Canyon.
- "Okay"?
- Follow that truck.
It's okay.
It's like they weren't even sure
they were filming a chase scene.
Radar makes two scenes
seem almost identical.
Hey, it's the... ♪ Friendless ranger
in the black sedan ♪
Jeez, this movie gets up
and stretches a lot, huh?
Sure do.
Hang the radar in a tree
or the bears might get it.
"I think I should take
my lobster bib off."
You sure this is the right spot?
I guess we're a little early.
They'll show up. Don't worry.
"Stainless steel
Swedish meatballs.
"All stainless, all Swedish,
all meatballs.
Get 'em here."
It's kind of like
Radar Obvious Service.
"What kind of sealant do you think
they use on this thing, huh?"
"Do you ever think about God?
He's up there, you know."
"Round things.
"Today we are promoting
round things.
Half off all round things."
So, Mike did you know
that Horshack's name
meant, "The cattle are dying"?
- Yes, I knew that.
- You did?
Yes.
"Attention all squirrels.
"Squirrels need round things, too.
"Think about it. You too, mule deer.
Round things."
It's a flying mantis!
♪♪
"Well, hello, Senator Johnson."
They're in a little clearing
behind those trees.
Get around behind them
and keep us covered.
"I just couldn't stop crying.
Oh, wait. Here they are."
Wow, that guy's snap brim
is working overtime.
♪ Golden Grahams ♪
Well, I see you made it.
- "You know Pie Face."
- "Hi, Tuna."
It's all there, all right.
How about the dough?
♪ Oh, those Golden Grahams ♪
( vocalizing )
It's all there. Pay 'em off.
"Hee, hee, hee.
Did I surprise you?"
- You'll never get away with this.
- "Copper."
Mike will want to see the money.
I got news for you.
This is Michael's idea.
- A double-cross, eh?
- Must we label everything?
All right, hold it!
"It's the triple-dog
dare double-cross dog..."
Oh, he got shot.
What a lucky guy.
"No radar necessary here.
Conventional warfare
does the trick."
( imitating bullets ricocheting )
"I'm gonna shoot too! Pow!"
"Um, I-I'll be right back.
"Just keep shooting.
I forgot to get this thing
that I got to get."
Radar was also used by
the Hatfields and McCoys.
Both sides.
Ah. ( chuckles )
Now everyone surrenders
to everyone else.
All: We all have the right
to remain silent.
Have the plane
keep them in sight.
Get me his bearing.
I'll be following in my car.
"Oh, my water broke. Ooh."
A daring high-speed chase
through Hugo, Minnesota!
"We have stainless steel truffles."
- "Do I get a lunch?"
- "No."
- "Is there a movie?"
- "No, there's nothing."
"Silver almond cookies
on sale now."
"The Hiller 460 at least
had an ashtray.
Can I smoke?"
"Anthony Robbins, father of five,
"involved in community affairs,
flies his own helicopter."
Well...
"Oh, why did I let her
pick this tie?"
"Hey, slug bug! Got one."
( vocalizing syncopated tune )
"I had to go pick up my brother
at the hospital,
"drop off the guns at Karen's house,
and then back to stir the sauce."
"I can't make it
to the next rest stop.
I've got to get a Big Gulp."
"Hugo, Minnesota,
encourages business development."
"I wish I had a dog."
You know, fellas,
I can just never get sick
of this shot here.
- I'm in with you.
- Yeah.
"I had to sell the guns
"so I could get enough money
to buy the coke,
"so I brought them back
to Karen's house,
"but her mother had to go get..."
OX-Q. OX-Q.
Car going northeast
over Pennsylvania Avenue.
"We're riding to work or play
in our helicopter."
( humming dramatic tune )
"Well, I've got my wigs,
and I'm ready for my stand-up act."
Let's get out of here.
Relax.
You're nervous as a cat.
I can't help it.
I'd feel a whole lot better
if we were on the yacht,
miles away from Mickey.
Forget about Mickey.
He won't bother you anymore.
My boys have taken care
of him by now.
You're wrong, brother.
"Oh, hi!"
It looks like we underestimated
Mr. Moran.
- Mickey, I didn't...
- Shut up.
Turn around, face the wall.
Both of you.
"I'll hike my pants up
even further."
"Okay, let's sing
'Somewhere Out There.'"
Why shoot me?
"Well, you're starting to leave
little accidents around the house."
It was Michael
who double-crossed you.
Be a crime to separate you two.
"Boy, that'd be really rotten
if you had a gun."
"Oh, thanks.
Right in the first wound. Ow!"
♪ Oh, those Golden Grahams,
oh, those Golden... ♪
"Oh, what? Now we're never
gonna get out of here."
Leaving without saying good-bye?
What do you want?
Get back in the other room so...
Wait, I thought that woman
was that woman.
- Yeah.
- Huh?
"Why don't you ask us
to turn around and face the wall?
Please?"
"How-How-How have you been?"
If it's Blackie you're
worrying about,
that's been all taken care of.
- Yeah?
- Sure.
I gave Mickey the money to spring him.
Didn't he tell you?
No, he didn't.
When did this happen?
- "Tomorrow?"
- He just left here a little while ago.
Said he was going
straight to the lawyer.
"Oh, that. I can explain that."
You didn't let him get very far.
When you're through with a boyfriend,
you're really through.
"Toilet tank floats.
Stop your toilet
from always flowing."
( vocalizing
Sanford and Son theme )
"All right. I'm going to show you
just how gullible I am."
"I'm gonna get coffee and a bear claw.
You want anything?"
Give me the police.
"Turn around and face the wall."
Police Department. Hello?
This wouldn't have happened
if she'd used AT&T.
Well, she's not dealing with AT&T.
"No substitutions."
"Oh, for the love of...
We just want to leave!"
Please, shoot them all.
Just let God sort them out.
Plot thickener.
- Hello? Police department.
- "Does it hurt when I..."
- "Ow!"
- "Oh, it does."
Police department. Hello?
"Hi, who are you holding for?"
This is Bill Travis, radar patrol.
Send homicide and an ambulance
to 416 State Street, apartment 4.
- He ordered more homicide?
- Sure.
Hey, it's the Sunday
Radar Supplement.
The data's in on those
Antarctic meteors.
"We've recovered the balance
of the atomic materials.
There might be some
floating around, but all in all..."
It didn't take long
to clean up that case.
- "Go home!"
- But before we take any bows,
let's remember
that if it hadn't been for radar,
we might never have
found them at all.
- That reminds me--
- "I like radar."
The budget for radar patrol
is being increased.
We'll be able to get
that extra equipment
- you were talking about.
- That's good news, Chief.
"And can we take
the thing off our car?"
How about loaning me
one of those telemeters?
My girl has a date tonight,
and I'd like to keep an eye on her.
Ha, ha! You always have
the last word, Howard.
- Not enough Sid Melton for my taste.
- Oh, never enough.
( all laughing )
Helicopters, dirt roads,
people standing around
ramrod-straight...
( laughing )
Ah, those Mads really
thought they had us.
- Thank God we had protection.
- You said it.
But just when the going got tough,
the tough got goofy!
That's right. The Mads may have
had hypno helio static stasis,
with all its doomsday ramifications,
but we-- we, gentlemen--
remembered to bring along
plenty of...
All:
Ecstato-euphoro-fun!
That's right-- ecstato-euphoro-fun,
with patented Hinder 90.
It takes a B-movie and turns it
into a "yippee!" movie.
Yippee! Hey, you know,
I think it's the Hinder 90
that made the helicopter sequence
so over-the-top funny!
True, true.
But it really proved itself
on those hard-to-get-at scenes,
like at the barn,
or how about the ground-in pain
of the office sequence?
Let's just face it--
ecstato-euphoro-fun,
with patented Hinder 90,
makes everything fun!
Bots:
Hooray!
Oh, what do you think, Pants?
Hinder 90...
Hey, Steve-orino.
Just ran into
Dr. "Vatshisname" out there.
Seems like you're really
kicking some...
Frank, the gig is up.
They've got Hinder 90.
Hinder 90? Hey!
There's no such thing
as Hinder 90.
- Is too.
- Is not.
- Is too. Hey!
Frank, as far as I'm concerned,
Nelson and I are in
an all-out arms race.
He's got Hinder 90,
and I'm behind.
"Behind!" "Hinder!"
Get it?
Frank, one more crack like that...
Cra...
( laughing )
They don't come
any better than TV's Frank.
( both gasp, sigh )
♪♪
( screaming )
Oh, there's a dead man!
It's all right, Myrtle.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you!